Your Scurvy Been
a Sour After varit Half five After varit
Half five
Alice!
Good morning!
Sugou!
Good morning.
What brings you here?
The weather's so nice.
I thought we could take a
walk to the eastern hill.
You, me, and Kirito, of course.
It is a lovely day.
The fresh air would do him good.
Shall we go then, Kirito?
I walk away
I walk away I walk
Oh In my ability we have been part
of the series We are going to feel
like we are one of the moments We
are going to make perfect at all
We are going to feel like no one
We believe that we are
the
strongest
There.
Let's get going.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll get them for you.
Be careful with them.
Hold them tight now.
I hope he is warm enough.
Sometimes you can be such a worrywart!
You bundled him up so much he's sweating!
Aren't you, Kirito?
I know you, Gio, think so.
How beautiful none of the paintings in
the cathedral can compare with this view.
You saved this world Kirito remember.
We're screwed what do
we do if they cut the
main power line now it's
gonna cause a surge?
A light cube cluster
should be safe but the
subcomputer where Kitty
Guy is STL is won't be.
The surge will cook his Fluctlight!
Okay, I'll handle the lockdown.
Higa, take Dr.
Kojiro and Asuna and
get to the upper shaft.
Keep Kirito safe. Asuna?
Kirito?
They're cutting the power!
The screw propellers are going down!
Kirito!
You cannot die!
Not after saving my life! Kirito!
Kirito!
Hey, kid.
Uncle.
What happened?
We're facing the biggest crisis in
the history of the Axiom Church.
Those two elite disciples we
fought killed the Pontifex.
No, it can't be.
She's dead? Impossible.
That's not all.
Judelkin died with the Pontifex.
With him gone, there's no more Senate.
This makes no sense.
Why would those disciples risk
angering the gods with their actions?
To stop the Pontifex before she turned
half the human realm into weapons of war,
an army of mindless living swords.
How could she do such a thing?
To subject the people to such horror?
It's diabolical.
Sir Bercoli, where are the two
rogues who murdered her eminence?
They must be captured and interrogated.
We don't have time to
deal with that right now.
The Dark Territory's been
itching to invade us.
And when they find out about
the Pontifex, they will.
Our ranks are half as strong thanks to
past battles with the forces of darkness.
We should all be worried about that.
If the Dark Territory decides to attack us
now, the Human Realm will fall for sure.
Then what should we do?
Or rather, what can we do?
First, we'll restore the Order
of the Integrity Knights.
Then we'll muster the Imperial Knights of
the Four Empires and
train them for battle.
There's strength in numbers, and right
now, we need all the help we can get.
I know what I told you was hard to accept,
but it's still our job to
protect the people here.
I can't do that without you.
Sir.
I wonder if Kirito's hungry.
There's a rumor going round, saying that
rebel swordsman is still alive. I heard.
He's supposed to be in a coma.
I know we have to prepare for
the Dark Territory to invade,
but leaving that traitor in our midst?
He defied the Church and should
be executed for it. Agreed.
Who knows what Commander
Bacoli is thinking.
It is no longer safe for Kirito here.
We shall go to Rulet Village.
Perhaps they will accept us there,
since it is the place where
Eugeo and I were born.
Hold on, you!
Strangers aren't allowed
in unless I say so!
What in the...
By the gods, it can't be...
I am no stranger.
I am Alice.
Summon Gasfut Zuburg at once.
Is that really you, Alice?
Yes.
Well then, what are you doing here?
Have you been pardoned for your crime?
Perhaps.
I certainly was punished for it.
All of the memories I had of
my life here were wiped away.
If that is not enough to absolve
me, no one said otherwise.
Regardless, I have returned, because
I could think of nowhere else to go.
Be gone.
We cannot allow a criminal to stay here.
What's wrong?
It is nothing.
Shall we start heading back?
Sure.
What is it, Selka?
Something troubles you.
Well, it's nothing
serious. It's Mr. Barbossa.
He asked if you could chop
down another tree for him.
Honestly, that's why you're so quiet?
You do know he and I have an agreement.
Yes, but how dare he?
The hypocrite!
Both him and Mr. Riddick.
They don't hesitate to ask you
for help when they need it,
but they don't mind you
being shunned by the village.
It's all right, Selka.
As long as I can have a place on
the outskirts, that's enough for me.
Yes, but next year, my training
will be done, and I was thinking,
since I'll be earning a little
money, I could give you that.
It's not much, but it's enough that you
won't have to help those people anymore.
You and Kirito don't have to worry.
I'll help somehow.
I'm grateful but having you close
by is all I could ever need.
I am happy just to have that.
Sugou
Why is this taking so long?
In the time it takes you
to cut this damn tree down,
Riddick's men will have expanded his
land 20 miles in order - Good day, Mr.
Barbossa.
Alice!
How good of you to come!
And so quickly, too!
I heard you need my assistance.
Yes.
It's that one over there.
We've been hacking away at
it since yesterday morning.
These damn platinum oak
trees are tough. Why,
ten grown men have put
their backs into every
swing and they've barely
made a scratch in it.
So I asked for you.
I know our deal is for one tree a month,
but this one's stubborn and I
really need your help here, Alice.
What do you say?
I shall do it. And happily.
But just this once, understood?
Great!
I knew I could count on you!
If you don't mind, Kirito, I need
your sword, but only for a moment.
Thank you.
Come on.
You think you're going to cut down a
platinum oak with a little old sword?
It'll snap in half.
Look at that.
She missed!
You'd best move away from there. What?
Why should we...
Oh. Splendid. Wonderful. Magnificent.
Your skill is unbelievable.
No, exceptional.
Hear me out now.
I shall double your compensation.
And instead of once a month,
you'd work for me once a week.
No once a day.
I know you could use the money.
Thank you, but the amount you are
paying now is quite sufficient
My payment oh of course yes right away
Thank you, mr.
Barbosa
What the?
It's so heavy.
How else do you think
she cut that tree down?
Anyone could with that sword.
Let me try.
That sword belongs to Kirito.
Get your hands off it.
We asked him.
If he didn't want us touching it,
he should have said something.
He's right.
We asked him nicely, and all he did
was go, uh, uh, like a gibbering fool.
Fine, take it.
It's just a damn sword.
Is this what we fought for, suffered
for, to protect people like these?
Eugeo lost his life.
Kirito is a shell of his former self.
If there is a point to all we've
been through, it is lost to me.
Amayori, it seems you've
gained some weight.
You've been gorging on too many fish.
Good night. Sleep well.
Here.
Don't eat too fast now.
Is that...?
Takiguri.
I'm Ayori's elder brother.
Which means...
I'm impressed you found us.
Now why have you come?
Eldrie Synthesis 31.
It has been far too long.
My lady. My mentor.
So how did you find me?
More importantly, why?
I'm sure the Order has
better things to do now
than send dragons all over
just to track me down.
You won't believe this, but I simply
followed the bond between our souls. Ha!
If only that were true.
No, I found you by complete coincidence.
Although, now that I am here, I have news.
The goblins and orcs have
been mobilizing in the north.
As for why I'm here,
the commander ordered us to collapse
the caves to the south and west and
here in the north i was sent to make
sure the fiends hadn't dug them out
and is the cave north of here safe
or have they dug through it i spent
all day up there keeping a vigilant
eye upon it in all that time i did not
spot any orcs or goblins i'm happy to
report the cave is still filled with
debris then as i made my way back to
the capital takiguri began behaving
strangely.
I allowed him free rein, and
this is where he chose to land.
Your new home, and
now that we've been reunited at last,
you will forgive me for speaking my mind.
Lady Alice, please return to the Order.
We need your sword now,
more than ever, more than an
army of thousands!
I cannot. Why not?
Is it because of that one?
The man who escaped from prison?
The man who flouted the law?
Who raised his sword
against your fellow knights,
the prime senator, and the pontifex?
Is he still leading your
heart astray?
If so, there is but one
solution for your confusion.
I shall eliminate him at once!
Stop it!
He fought not for himself, but
for what he believed was right.
For justice.
Is that not what the
knighthood fights for?
He defeated us one after the other.
including the commander.
When you fought him, surely you could
feel the purity of his conviction?
and the weight of his sword.
If he is as pure as you say, then why
won't he take up his sword and help us now?
How could he allow himself to be
reduced to such a pathetic state?
and shackle you to these hinterlands?
If what I heard is true!
And he killed the Pontifex
for the sake of the people,
Then it is his duty to join
them at the Eastern Gate.
and defend the land!
Forgive me, Eldrie.
But I cannot go with you
to assist in the battle.
It has nothing to do with him.
I can no longer wield my sword.
That is the reason.
If you and I cross swords now, I
doubt I would last three strikes.
Is that so?
All right, I will not press you further.
I bid you farewell, m 'lady.
You were my mentor,
and as long as I live, I shall
never forget all you have taught me.
Farewell, then.
I pray you'll be safe.
It's gotten late.
You must be tired.
Let's get you to bed, shall we?
Tell me, Kirito.
What should I do?
What is it? What's wrong?
A fire!
The Dark Territory is attacking!
Sugou!
Next time, the attack.